{
  "extraDescription": "NB: first operand may not be divisible by second operand",
  "openingRemarks": "NB: You can enter 'U' or 'unexpected' for results which are not expected or defined",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "45 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 6",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 3",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "63 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "-7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 4",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "-40 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "-5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-48 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "-12",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 2",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "-1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "88 &#xF7; 11",
      "answer": "8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 4",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "21 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 2",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-120 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "37 &#xF7; -5",
      "answer": "-7 2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "-24 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-21 &#xF7; 4",
      "answer": "-5 1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "23 &#xF7; -2",
      "answer": "-11 1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "-38 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "4 2/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "60 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-9 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-40 &#xF7; 5",
      "answer": "-8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "24 &#xF7; -4",
      "answer": "-6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "-30 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "72 &#xF7; -12",
      "answer": "-6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &#xF7; -3",
      "answer": "-4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "83 &#xF7; -9",
      "answer": "-9 2/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "42 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-110 &#xF7; 10",
      "answer": "-11",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 3",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "-55 &#xF7; -11",
      "answer": "5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "108 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "72 &#xF7; 12",
      "answer": "6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &#xF7; 0",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "undefined"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &#xF7; 1",
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ],
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "49 &#xF7; 7",
      "answer": "7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "-3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "43 &#xF7; 8",
      "answer": "5 3/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "acceptNanAnswer": true
    },
    {
      "question": "-8 &#xF7; 2",
      "answer": "-4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "mix"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0
      ]
    }
  ]
}
